(A Bona fide Killer)
(This drama, its characters,
and events are fictional.)
(Scenes with child actors
and animals were supervised.)
(2018 South Korea VS Germany)
- Korea.
(Episode 7)
Pickpockets are running wild
in the square,
taking advantage of the World Cup crowds.
Pickpockets. Pickpockets.
I love soccer, but I'm telling you,
I'm not here for fun.
Who knows? They might even put out
a composite sketch of me.
And I've prepared the perfect bait.
I'm hanging up.
Hey. You in the red hat. Stop.
That one's a fake.
This is the real one, full of cash.
Darn it...
If you don't want your picture taken,
let's at least do an interview.
The old man says to lie low for a while.
And you know I always listen
to our money man.
But I heard
that delivery schmuck who died
was a widower with two kids.
Dude, of all the people
to hit with your car...
What the hell are you talking about?
The front of my quarter-million-dollar car
is totaled.
I'm the victim here.
Hey, hey, we scored a goal.
- Hey, they scored.
- So what?
Hello?
I'm so damn annoyed right now,
and these pathetic losers...
Korea's a damn honey pot, you bastards.
Meeting's over.
Is it over?
It's finally over.
Relax, rookie.
And stretch out that cramp in your leg.
What? Nervous? I wasn't...
Half of any Meeting is just waiting.
And what else do you need?
Endurance.
I guess I need to do
some strength training.
Nice work.
You're pretty skilled too, rookie.
I can leave things in your hands.
What?
Leave? Where? Who's leaving?
That was excellent for a first Meeting.
Good job.
Take the emergency stairs
to the first floor.
Go out through Gate Three
and blend into the crowd.
Okay.
But what about you?
It's too bad you're missing the game.
I'm not interested.
Really? That's unusual.
You're not interested either, are you?
That must be why you scheduled
the Meeting for today.
Hey, that's because a day like today
is advantageous for a Meeting.
But besides work,
do you have any other interests?
Are you picking up any movement right now?
Near the emergency stairs?
What?
No. Besides the security office,
the entire building is empty.
Then rewind and check
if we missed anything.
From after I came up.
Is something wrong?
Report back if you find anything.
(Resident Id Card: Kwon Tae Sung)
(Reporter, Not Today, Kwon Tae Sung)
(Gate 3)
(Emergency Stairs Exit)
Hey.
About 10 minutes ago,
2 men ran in through Gate 3.
It looked like one was chasing the other.
They entered the emergency stairs
one after the other,
and five minutes later,
only the one who went in first came out.
I missed it.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay. Keep your eyes on it.
But what's...
You should have been more careful.
(Connecting to Emergency Services: 911)
Yes, this is the Kingtower Building.
On the fifth floor
of the emergency stairwell,
there's a man collapsed
and bleeding from his head.
I think he'll die if you don't hurry.
Try to live, if you can.
It looks like we won the soccer game.
Because one is enough for today.
(4 Months Later)
- Hold still. Stay still.
- Why? Goodness.
- Let me see for a second.
- What? Seriously, what's wrong?
Your head's still attached.
You're insane, aren't you?
That's right. I can start walking today.
Hey, hey.
This feels weird.
If you see a pickpocket,
you're supposed to call the police.
- Why would you chase them, you idiot?
- I think I have a cramp.
How can you lecture me
about the same thing every time you visit?
You're unbelievable.
I'm so sick of hearing it.
You think this is funny?
You're laughing right now?
You woke up after four months, you idiot.
Calling a patient with a head injury
an idiot over and over.
Right. You still haven't caught the guy
who hit me from behind.
- Don't you dare go trying to catch him.
- Why?
You look like you'd actually kill him
if you caught him.
Of course I'd kill him.
That bastard. You...
The rooftop of the building
where you collapsed,
did you know that was
Kingfisher's sniping point?
I know. It's such a shame, seriously.
If I hadn't been hit
in the back of the head,
- I could have met Kingfisher.
- You could have met them, I guess.
But you'd have a hole
in your head instead, you idiot.
Hey, that's slander against Kingfisher.
Why? Because I'm an innocent civilian.
I can't tell if this guy is lucky
or unlucky.
I really worry about the kind of woman
who'll end up with you.
(Ward 22)
Manager Yu, you visit so often.
You're making me feel bad.
It's not like being sick is a big deal.
You were injured on the job.
How are you feeling?
Maybe it's my age,
but this isn't healing well.
I know. Everyone's going through a lot
because of me.
Everyone is very worried.
You know you need to be careful...
about aftereffects
from the car accident, right?
Well, this...
Darn...
This is good.
Oh man, this...
- This?
- Yes.
By the way,
I hear the new recruit
is pretty competent.
Yes, after Assistant Manager Son quit,
I was worried his absence
would leave a big hole.
But now I can breathe a sigh of relief.
Your absence is felt even more, sir.
Please get well soon and come back.
I can't leave with peace of mind
until you're back.
Manager Yu, have you made up your mind?
Are you really going to quit?
I think I'm just worn out.
Yes, that's understandable.
Even ordinary people,
after working for ten years,
they say they experience
that thing, burnout.
You've done nothing but work
without a break,
so it's no wonder you're exhausted.
Right?
Besides, your line of work
isn't exactly ordinary, is it?
It's a thankless job that never ends.
And the world never changes.
I completely understand how you feel.
Manager Yu.
Won't you please reconsider?
Don't go to the field Meetings
for a while.
Just take it easy.
Okay?
Just a moment. Just...
Get down. Come down, quickly.
Okay, easy now. Be careful.
Why?
What?
Why? Why?
Why?
Because life is precious.
What I mean is...
I recently had a near-death experience,
and it made me realize something. So...
You know, you look at the sky,
you look at the autumn leaves.
I'm glad to be alive.
It's so good to be alive.
You get to joke around with your friends,
get nagged by your family.
What should I eat today?
What should I wear tomorrow?
An ordinary life where you worry
about such trivial things...
is so precious. Truly precious.
That's why I...
hope that you will choose to live.
Someone who says life is precious
is smoking a cigarette?
Especially after a near-death experience.
Doesn't that seem wrong to you?
This isn't mine. I was just on my way...
Live a good life.
Enjoy your ordinary, day-to-day life.
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
No.
But I'm sure I've seen you before...
Your voice sounds familiar too.
I'm sorry. I...
I hurt my head,
so I think my mind's a little fuzzy.
I guess my memory will come back
once I recover. Right?
Kwon Tae Sung.
He's a reporter for an online news outlet.
I looked through some of
his past articles,
and his main interests are social justice
and protecting the weak.
He's a rare breed of reporter these days.
But why him?
- Just a precaution. Keep going.
- Is it because of this?
(Kingfisher)
It seems he's written all of
this outlet's articles on Kingfisher.
I skimmed through them,
and he didn't really have a negative take
on Kingfisher.
It was more about analyzing the phenomenon
than following the incidents.
So among others in the industry
and readers,
they seem to be well-regarded
as in-depth articles.
And he also has a personal blog.
Send me the link.
And the articles. Right now.
All of them?
I mean, she usually couldn't care less
about articles...
Kingfisher, Unprecedented
Murderer or Arbiter of Justice?
The Painful Questions Kingfisher Raises
for Our Society.
Five Reflections on Kingfisher.
Is Our Judicial System
Sufficiently Trustworthy?
If I Were to Meet Kingfisher.
Fortunately, I had a smooth upbringing
in a happy home,
and throughout my school years,
I was an ordinary, model student
for the most part.
Best two out of three?
Loser buys pizza.
Don't be a sore loser, or you're dead.
You're the one who shouldn't be crying
when you lose, you jerk.
- Hey, how many times have you lost?
- Whatever.
If it weren't
for the tragic incident
that befell a friend of mine,
I might have lived my whole life
far removed...
from things like crime and illegal acts.
A murder involving
a sniper rifle has occurred...
in the heart of downtown Seoul.
- According to police, Semyeong-dong...
- A gun?
- A man in his 40s was shot...
- What are they going to do?
I still remember the shock
of when I first learned of his existence.
To think there was someone
who only targeted vicious criminals,
the kind who destroy the lives
of ordinary, innocent people.
Honestly, isn't Kingfisher kind of cool?
What's cool about him?
He's just a crazy murderer.
Hey, but he only kills bad guys.
Hey, even if he only kills
bad guys, a murderer is still a murderer.
While the world was loudly
debating and taking sides,
I found myself wondering.
What kind of person would risk
their entire life...
to do something like that?
(Reporter Attacked By Pickpockets
Wakes After Four Months)
At the time of the incident, Reporter Kwon
was in a building in downtown Seoul...
(Rooftop Where Reporter Kwon Collapsed
Was Kingfisher's Sniping Position)
Have we met before?
Once I've fully recovered,
my memories will slowly come back, right?
(Gyeongsan Hospital)
(2018 First-Class ICU Rating)
- You didn't make this.
- I did make it.
- You bought this.
- No, I made it. Try some.
- How is it?
- Tastes store-bought.
No, it doesn't.
I really, really made this. I'm serious.
How about this one?
- It's good.
- That's it?
What? What else am I supposed
to say? It's...it's good.
I made it, and I think
I did a really good job.
Excuse me, miss! Just a moment.
I finally found her.
I've been waiting for you. Every day.
Why?
Because I remembered where we met.
You lived in Hoehun-dong as a kid, right?
No, I've never lived there.
You went to Jeongin Middle School,
didn't you? I'm right, aren't I?
No.
- The Hwaljjak Binnari Academy...
- No.
Has anyone told you
you look like the actress Choi So Hyun...
No, they haven't. Right.
I'm sorry.
I'll try to jog my memory better,
and I'll be sure
to get it right next time.
You might be misunderstanding this,
thinking I'm hitting on you,
but that's not it at all. Absolutely not.
If we happen to have a chance
to meet again...
No, that's not going to happen.
Don't do anything pointless.
We've never met.
Gosh.
(Gyeongsan Hospital Screening Center)
I should have asked for her name.
Are you having trouble sleeping?
You wake up soon after falling asleep,
and you have nightmares sometimes?
Yes, I guess.
Have you been under
a lot of stress recently?
Maybe some trouble in your relationships,
or feeling pressured at work?
- No, I haven't.
- No, not at all.
I see. I can prescribe you
a higher dose of sleeping pills, but...
in my opinion...
Are you having fun?
Mi Ju, how do you like it? Is it okay?
But isn't it really pretty here?
- Really? Good job.
- You want to hold it?
No.
Hey, we won over here. Mom.
(Team Leader Bae Yoon OK, Sales Team 3)
I'm resigning.
Please accept it, Team Leader.
- He's coming out.
- There he is. Excuse me.
Do we know how two people
were taken down in the same room?
What if there was only one target,
- and Kingfisher made a mistake?
- We're not police officers.
We're just office workers
on our lunch break.
- They said they aren't.
- They're not cops?
What's going on?
You're a good liar.
Well, I was half-telling the truth.
It's true that we're not the cops
in charge of this jurisdiction.
I'm so hungry I could pass out.
All I had last night were
two of those chocolate pies.
I only had one cream bun.
Oh, right.
Goodness.
But I guess "One shot, two kills"
is a hot topic, as expected.
It's the 1st case like it in 16 years.
The internet is going crazy over it too,
that the original target
was just Tak Jong Gu,
and that they accidentally killed
an innocent person trying to shoot him.
Do you really think Kingfisher is someone
who would make that kind of mistake?
Oh, no. He's not that type at all.
Anyway, setting Tak Jong Gu aside.
What did that Chairman Cheon
what's-his-name do to deserve it?
That's what we need to find out now.
Why Cheon Seong Gil was a target.
Right now? Without eating first?
Come on, sir,
I've only had two chocolate pies...
Hey, wait up.
This case is unusual
not only because there were two deaths,
but because the criminal history...
of one of the victims
hasn't been identified.
This has led to speculation
that Kingfisher may have mistakenly...
killed an innocent person.
If that turns out to be true,
it could cause
a major shift in public opinion, right?
Until now, the belief was
that he only killed vicious criminals...
- Yes, Reporter Koo.
- Hey, where are you?
The informant
on the Cheon Seong Gil case called.
They're willing to do an interview.
I've arranged to meet them right now.
Hello?
Hey? Are you there? Are you listening?
Where did you agree to meet?
(Taesung Chicken)
- I'm here, Mother.
- Oh, welcome...
What are you doing here at this hour?
- Didn't you go to work?
- No, my business trip ended a day early,
so I don't have to go in today.
And I bought you something, Mother.
Oh? What's this?
(Lipiera)
Since you haven't been sleeping well
at night lately,
and you've been having
hot and cold flashes.
I have been feeling flushed lately, but...
I wonder why that is.
Mother, they say it's all
because of menopause.
But one of these a day
can help you manage...
Really.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Help with what?
You must be tired from your trip.
Go home and get some rest.
No, I'm fine.
It's not like you're trying to mock me.
Hey, if you have eyes, take a look.
Is there anything here to help with?
My goodness.
Even if there was, so what?
Do you think I could
bring myself to ask you?
As if I'd dare to overwork
my precious daughter-in-law.
Then I'd just get an earful
from my son again.
Mom, why are you
taking it out on her again?
- No, it's fine.
- Business is slow,
so she's just taking it out on you.
Mother, this also helps with
mood swings from menopause.
So, what should I peel?
What?
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Welcome. Oh my.
Welcome. Please have a seat here.
Yes, sit right here.
President Kim, what a surprise.
I was just at
the Merchants' Association meeting.
- We came for lunch after it ended.
- Thank you.
About 20 more people will be coming later.
The manager of the senior center
in the next town...
was looking for a good chicken place,
- so I recommended you.
- Oh my goodness.
President Kim, you're a lifesaver.
A true lifesaver.
Just wait a moment.
I'll make it delicious for you.
Order whenever you're ready, okay?
Yes, Taesung Chicken.
Yes, the child welfare center?
Yes, I know it.
Yes. What? Twenty chickens?
By five o'clock?
Yes. We'll make them delicious
and send them over. Okay.
Twenty Chickens?
- Yes.
- What is happening?
What do you mean? It's our lucky day.
Quick, fry the chicken, fry the chicken.
Okay.
We're in trouble, the chicken...
Oh my, now we're really in a jam.
Is Yul's mom still here?
Mother, I'm right here.
- Thank you for your time today.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
- Get home safe now.
Take care.
This worked out so well, didn't it?
I was wondering how I'd write the article
without testimony or evidence.
It couldn't have been easy,
but she worked up the courage.
What, an innocent life?
He has no idea how evil a man
Cheon Seong Gil is.
Let's go.
But seriously,
your instincts are incredible.
It was the same with Pyo Gyu Cheol.
How do you manage to pinpoint
Kingfisher's targets like that?
At this rate...
Don't you think we might run into
Kingfisher somewhere?
I wonder if we've already
crossed paths without knowing.
Reporter Koo, aren't you scared?
About what might happen
if you meet Kingfisher?
What? Of what?
I'm an innocent citizen.
Let's go.
- It's hot, so please be careful.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
- One more fried chicken.
One fried chicken. Hey,
another order of fried chicken.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- Excuse me, one coke, please.
- You want a coke?
I'll get the coke. Here you go.
Take these empty glasses.
Yes, Mother.
Would you like some more pickled radish?
Okay, here's the coke.
- More sauce?
- Yes.
Just a moment, please.
- Here's a soda on the house.
- Enjoy, and please come again.
We'll put your donation
to the Merchants' Association to good use.
It would be good to publicize this
to show our support for our tenants,
but it's a shame
you wish to remain anonymous.
Thank you for the chicken.
My kids are so excited.
We will really enjoy it.
Thank you.
- In the VIP lounge of the casino...
- Yes, what can I get for you?
The sniper incident
that killed Chairman Cheon...
is once again gaining public attention.
Chairman Cheon, known as
Kingfisher's first civilian victim,
was considered an entrepreneur
who contributed...
greatly to the Gangwon region's economy...
I knew something like this would happen.
He was getting cocky,
calling himself a hero.
If they killed an innocent person,
they deserve to be punished too.
Kingfisher should be locked up.
I'll get you the sauce.
Hey, one more order of sauce.
- Sauce, got it.
- Okay.
- When is the fried chicken coming out?
- The fried chicken? When is it ready?
- It's ready now.
- It'll be right out.
Along with the precise details
of Chairman Cheon's death,
authorities are also expanding their
investigation into Kingfisher's motive.
What do these people take Kingfisher for?
What are we going to do?
Manager Yu is going to be so upset
when she finds out.
She'll be devastated.
For 16 years,
it's the most important principle
she has strictly upheld.
(Kingfisher:
First Innocent Civilian Victim?)
Manager Yu sent a text.
What does it say?
(Trustworthy Police, Safe Nation)
Hey, get rid of the reporters at the door.
Damn it. That bastard Kingfisher...
Why the hell did he come to this
backwater town to stir up trouble?
What a mess.
Gosh, what have you been digging for
all this time?
You went to the scene, didn't you?
Anyone could see that...
their two heads just happened
to line up at that exact moment.
Looks like Chairman Cheon
has a criminal record.
You mean the rape case?
Oh, that was a long time ago.
(Two Construction Workers Died)
What about the two workers who died
at a construction site recently?
That was ruled long ago
as an accidental fall and a suicide.
Those cases were closed.
I mean,
reporters came snooping around about that,
but there was nothing there,
so it never became a story.
- Unbelievable.
- We have breaking news.
The casino incident,
which was thought to involve
Kingfisher's first civilian victim...
Sir. Sir, look at that.
- Chairman Cheon's...
- Turn it up.
The full story has been revealed.
According to one news report,
Chairman Cheon...
hired the wife of one
of his construction workers...
as a housekeeper...
and then repeatedly
sexually assaulted her.
- When her husband later found out...
- No way.
and urged him to confess to the police,
Cheon bribed another worker...
- to have the husband murdered.
- What... What is that?
This was revealed
by the construction worker's wife herself.
This should put to rest the controversy
that Kingfisher had claimed...
their first innocent victim.
Police are confirming the facts
of the report,
and they are also looking into
additional criminal allegations...
- against Chairman Cheon...
- Nice.
Launched an internal investigation.
Online, Kingfisher is...
Reporter Koo, congratulations.
A total scoop.
Yes, thank you.
(Investigative Reporting Team)
Reporter Koo.
Is a rookie really allowed
to get an exclusive this fast?
You are making us seniors look bad.
- You have to treat us. You have to.
- Well, it was not really my exclusive...
Oh, come on.
We have someone this talented
at our company?
How did you land a story like this?
Like I said, I did not actually land it...
She says she will treat us, Director.
Come on now.
Squeezing blood from a stone?
Hey, she has to.
It is her first exclusive.
(Chairman Cheon Who Was Targeted,
Habitual Sex Assault, Contract Killing)
(The "Innocent Victim" Theory Is Debunked)
(Reporter Koo Hae Na,
Investigative Reporting Team)
The last meeting...
Move it up.
Today, if possible.
Today?
Make a noise in the east...
then strike in the west.
Where is Tae Min?
When was the last time
you washed your hair?
Do you not wash your clothes?
Do you not change your socks?
At least keep your shoes on.
Have you no consideration
for your partner?
Your hair is greasy,
and your clothes are filthy.
And the car reeks.
At this rate, I am going to suffocate
before we even get to the Meeting.
What? What are you doing?
So this is where it was.
Darn it.
This is not the fieldwork I dreamed of.
My dream was to one day
work with Kingfisher...
He ordered a lot of food.
This looks delicious.
Man, I am starving. Darn, I am hungry.
All right, let's see.
Sweet and sour pork.
Chili pepper japchae.
And jjajangmyeon.
The bastard who burned
his own parents to death
is stuffing his face.
Unbelievable.
He only got six years for killing
his parents for the inheritance?
Diminished capacity,
and 50 pages of apologies a day.
Everyone knows that.
That bastard is completely faking it...
What?
Damn it, this stupid fly... Shit.
Damn it.
What the hell? What is happening?
What happened? Come on.
Oh, come on. Seriously.
It is a ten-millimeter
concentrate of Mist.
The shell is water-soluble,
so it dissolves on contact with water,
and death occurs in under five minutes.
It decomposes within an hour,
so it will not show up in an autopsy.
Ten seconds left on the clock.
There is no time left. Hurry up.
Now, five seconds left.
Four, three, two, one.
He takes the shot.
Three-point line, a three-pointer.
Is it in? Is it in?
It's in!
A three-point buzzer-beater.
Damn it. See? You can do it.
What a grand finale.
You should have played like that
from the start.
They are getting ready for the playoffs.
Meeting clear.
Nice!
Farewell.
When you meet your parents,
be sure to apologize to them.
You rotten bastard.
Since we successfully
wrapped up our last Meeting,
let's have a team dinner for a change.
How about some beef? Yes, let's get beef.
By the way, this month's operating budget
is finalized.
Okay.
Okay, then how about beef?
Let's get beef!
How about beef? Let's get beef!
It's not your fault
that Yul is missing.
So please don't cry. I'll find her.
When you can't stop thinking
about someone all day,
and you smile every time, is that love?
Busy.
I think I'm in love.
(Se Ah: I Think I'm In Love.)
(Horaengsseu: Lol)
Forget it. What would you know about love?
What would you know?
You've never dated.
Look who's talking.
Then give me some advice.
I've never felt this way before,
so I don't know what to do.
First, ask to meet him.
You have to meet up to get dumped.
Can I really do that?
Or create a chance
to meet him naturally.
How?
Busy.
He doesn't know either.
A chance to meet them naturally?
Seriously.
Aunt Se Ah, what brings you here
at this hour?
I came to see Yul.
- Auntie.
- This looks delicious.
Sangju dried persimmons. Yul's favorite.
Aah!
Here comes the airplane.
Open wider.
Captain, that's not the correct route.
I will change course.
No. Not this way.
Captain, I don't want to eat.
- Dad.
- Delicious.
Yul, open wide.
Hm!
- It's delicious.
- It is, right? Go on.
Work must be really tough these days.
Not at all. Your brother helps me out
so much. It's fine.
And I have you to count on too.
Oh, I haven't done anything.
Se Ah, are you here for your allowance?
Of course not.
What about your coworkers?
Are they nice to you?
They're so helpful.
I'm settling in without any problems.
They must all be really nice people.
Shouldn't you treat them to a meal
or something?
- All of a sudden?
- Have you ever had a housewarming party?
A housewarming party?
You invite them over,
give them a tour of the house,
and treat them to a meal,
that kind of thing.
No, I've never thought about it.
Don't you know it's just as important
for a husband to support
his wife's career?
Working moms have to walk on eggshells
at the office.
If you take care of things like this,
her life at work will be easier.
You have a point.
You just returned to work
after three years,
and they're the wonderful people
who are taking such good care of you.
You should make them a nice, warm meal
to show your gratitude. Right?
That's what makes life worth living.
Just think of it as a work dinner.
Mm-hmm.
A work dinner?
(Durumi Electronics)
Manager Yu...
Why would she invite us to her home?
It's true she's never had anyone over.
Don't you think it's some kind of tactic
to blend in?
Our Manager Yu is not the type
to play games like that.
What should we get her as a gift?
Nothing beats toilet paper.
So that everything goes smoothly for them.
Come on, diffusers are the trendy gift
these days.
How about a set of wine glasses?
The wine itself is better
than the glasses.
By the way,
isn't Manager Tae Min going with us?
Oh, Manager Tae Min
doesn't really go out,
except for meetings.
He's a total homebody.
Right. It'd be an imposition
since they have a child.
Oh, how about a mood lamp
for a nice touch?
Let's just keep it simple.
You know what I mean, right?
We'll get the wine that I like.
He had his mind made up the whole time.
Pork belly, short ribs.
- On sale today.
- The short ribs.
- Come and take a look.
- Okay.
- Pork belly and short ribs are...
- How about this one?
This one. It's big. So big, right?
Okay.
What's next on the list?
Pollock and two mackerels. Right?
Hm?
- Let's go.
- Mom, squid, squid.
You want to get squid now?
Veggies, veggies.
Should we get veggies now?
Okay, then we'll be all done.
- Then what else was there?
- Look at the cart.
Wow, she's so excited.
We should have done this sooner.
But you know,
your wife is a real mystery.
There's so much she hasn't done
or experienced.
Seriously,
what kind of life has she lived?
Do you know anything?
Huh?
What? I'm her husband. Of course I know.
He has no idea.
Hey.
- Hey, can you get a cart? A cart.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Oh, Se Ah, hold on.
Oh, that hacker
who came to the playground.
You know, your colleague.
Oh, Ki Young Do.
Oh, so his name is Ki Young Do.
What a name...
Don't worry.
Thanks.
So, what kind of food does he like?
I'm not sure.
Well, I'm just so grateful to him
for helping us find Yul.
As a thank-you.
As a thank-you,
even if it's just one side dish,
I thought it would be right
to add something he likes.
That's a good point.
What should I make?
He's a picky eater.
Oh, he's a picky eater.
Even so, is there anything
he still seems to enjoy?
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello, it's nice to meet you.
- Yes, hello. Please, come on in. Come in.
- Please, come in.
- Let's see. Pardon the intrusion.
She has a nice home.
- Come in, come in.
- Okay, yes.
- Honey.
- Yes?
- They're here.
- You made it.
Thank you all for coming.
This is my husband, Kwon Tae Sung.
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
I'm sorry it's taken so long
to have you over.
Thank you so much for coming.
We're the ones who should be thanking you
for inviting us.
Not at all.
Gosh, your husband is very handsome.
Yul, say hello.
These are Mommy's friends from work.
- Hello.
- Hi. So you're Yul.
Hey, mind if we look around the house?
- Of course. Go ahead.
- Make yourselves at home.
Yes, come on in.
Make yourselves at home.
You all brought so much.
- They are all for you.
- You can definitely tell
a child lives here. It's so charming.
Half the stuff in here
belongs to the baby.
So I'm finally here.
I was so curious what it was like inside.
Mom! Aunt Se Ah looks like a princess.
She does, doesn't she?
This is my youngest sister.
She was here to help out today, and...
Your sister helps with
your housewarming party?
She's so sweet.
It's nice to meet you all.
My name is Kwon Se Ah.
Honey.
Have you been drinking?
This is an incredible feast.
You didn't make all this yourself,
did you?
So you're saying you really made
this entire feast by yourself?
I suggested we order a few things,
but she insisted on
making everything herself.
I made it all.
For a housewarming party,
personally preparing the food with care...
is what makes it meaningful.
This dish is a mix of glass noodles,
meat, and vegetables.
A classic celebratory dish
with beautiful colors.
A meat dish that truly makes you feel
like an honored guest.
And these savory pancakes are easy to eat,
but you can feel the effort
that went into them.
I made them.
Really, thank you for helping me adjust
after I came back to work.
I'm so grateful to all of you.
I wanted to personally make a warm meal
for you all.
I've been wanting to find a chance
to say this...
It's not much, but please enjoy.
What do you mean?
You've prepared so much.
- I'm going to eat so much today.
- Eat up.
Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal.
Come on, everyone, eat.
Please, enjoy.
I heard from my sister-in-law
that you enjoy this from time to time,
Assistant Manager Ki.
So I prepared some for you.
Please enjoy.
Go ahead and eat.
- Want some ribs? I'll cut them for you.
- Yes.
Here, I'll do it. You eat.
You didn't even have lunch.
You eat a lot.
Would you like some of that?
Mmm! You two are so sweet.
May I ask how you two first met?
We...
We just met here and there.
Actually, a pickpocket
brought us together.
A pickpocket?
Yes. About eight years ago,
I was covering a pickpocketing story,
and I ended up with a serious head injury.
Oh my, so you were
in a terrible situation.
But luckily, a woman called 911 for me,
and I barely made it out alive.
The hospital told me that
if I'd arrived any later,
I might not have made it.
So after I woke up
about four months later...
The first time I could walk,
I went up to the hospital rooftop,
and that's when I met Bo Na.
That day, I saw Bo Na's bright smile,
and I fell in love at first sight.
How romantic!
So you two have a love story like that.
That's so moving.
To think you were brought together
- on the verge of life and death.
- It is.
By any chance,
the woman who called 911 back then...
Do you know who she was?
I actually looked into it
with the 911 dispatch center...
as soon as I woke up,
but the call was made from my phone,
so they couldn't get her contact info.
And they only remembered
that the caller was a woman.
Well, I'm sure she'll be
greatly rewarded for that.
She's the one who saved your life. Right?
Then isn't the woman
the one who brought you together,
not the pickpocket?
Now that you mention it, you're right.
I should find her somehow
and thank her, right?
Oh, you should.
- You just have to find her.
- Yes, I will.
- Come on, dig in.
- It's getting cold. Please, eat up.
Here, Assistant Manager Ki.
You should have some meat too,
Assistant Manager Ki. Here.
Oh no. Just a second. This...
- Oh no.
- Oh, what do I do? This wet wipe...
I'm so sorry, Assistant Manager Ki.
I'm all right.
Do you have any cold beer?
Beer? I'll get some for you right away.
Here, I'll open it for you.
Oh no.
At least take this...
(8 Years Ago, Spring)
I've never applied to this company.
There must be some kind of mistake...
You must have been surprised to have
an application sent by email so suddenly.
You were kidnapped as a child.
Your major is psychology,
but your specialty is hacking.
Durumi Electronics Sales Team Three.
I think you do things differently
from the other departments.
Please continue.
Even your transaction performance chart...
looks subtly different
from other departments,
as if you pieced it together
by splicing real data.
The same goes for the ratio
of off-site work in your logs.
So, did you figure out what they do?
Only that it's illegal.
That's right.
Sales Team Three carefully selects
and eliminates criminals.
For various reasons,
I'm pleased with your qualifications,
Mr. Ki Young Do.
What happens if I refuse?
We only make offers to people
who won't refuse.
Still, if I refuse, will you kill me?
You need to keep it a secret.
What will you do? Will you keep my secret?
Don't be such a chicken.
Eat this and relax, rookie.
This is the best thing for stress. Eat up.
I'm so screwed.
Oh, I should just leave this house.
I should just go die.
Oh dear.
Let's have some fruit.
Yul, come here.
Oh, Yul, want some strawberries?
Okay, let's toast. Cheers.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
I'll be heading out first.
- Where do you think you're going?
- This is perfect.
Since Assistant Manager Ki is leaving,
so you should walk him to the main road.
He's taking the subway,
so go to the back gate.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Why?
- What? He doesn't know the way.
Oh, right. Assistant Manager Ki,
go on ahead.
- We'll leave in a little bit.
- Go on.
All right, everyone.
- Cheers.
Assistant Manager Ki.
I'll be sure to wash your clothes
and return them.
Fine.
Are you very upset?
I'm not thrilled.
Oh, so you're not thrilled.
This is all because of me...
Can't your brother lift a finger?
Lift a finger?
When are you going to return my clothes?
Soon? Yes.
The day you return the clothes,
let's go on a date.
A date?
That was a great meal.
I ate so well. I'm so full.
Oh, by the way, we did a good job, right?
Yes, I think we did well.
We didn't make any mistakes, did we?
- I don't think we made any mistakes.
- Right. Good.
Honestly, Manager Yu's cooking
is just so-so, right?
Oh, my goodness.
Do you think we won't need to erase
that CCTV record?
Oh, Team Leader.
We didn't come here for a Meeting today.
Right. Hey, let's just act normal.
Act normal, okay?
Get in.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
I think you might have dropped this.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- Uncle.
- Gosh, my little princess.
- Hey.
- Wow, my little princess.
Uncle, did you catch a lot of bad guys?
I caught this many.
Okay, Yul. Come on.
All right, attention.
This uncle protects good kids like Yul.
I'm a...
- Policeman.
- That's right. Good job.
- Let's go.
- You're early, guess you're not busy.
Hey, Bo Na said she's making
braised short ribs.
What could be more important than that?
Now, go play.
Dong Jin, you're here.
Thank you for having me over again.
Oh, it was nothing.
Why does she always insist on inviting you
whenever she cooks?
- It's a bad habit.
- Why?
It means that
while I'm unlucky in friends,
I'm very lucky
when it comes to their wives.
You should worry about
finding your own wife.
You should come by more often.
Yul gets really excited
when she hears you're coming over, Uncle.
You got it. I'll do that.
Anyway, it must be tough for you
now that you're back at work.
You should make this guy help you more.
He's always been so coddled,
so I doubt there's much
he knows how to do.
I'm actually good at everything now.
All right?
Honey, what else should I do?
Just say the word.
His heart's in the right place.
He's just not very talented...
Just a moment. I'll go get you something.
Thank you. I'm in your debt.
- Sit down.
- No, it's all right.
Looks like you had company?
Yeah, my wife's coworkers.
Oh, that must've been them
leaving just now.
- You saw them?
- Yes, by the first-floor elevator.
They seemed really nice.
I'll have home-cooked meals for a week.
Seriously, Bo Na... Every time...
I helped with that.
- You should thank me.
- For which part?
Tell me so I can throw it out right now.
Will you?
You said you'd repay us, right? With what?
Do I have money?
Do I have connections?
Wow, you're already going back
on your word.
As a cop, the only thing I know how to do
is protect people.
Except for you, you jerk.
I'm only going to protect
sweet Bo Na and lovely Yul.
I can protect my own wife and daughter.
Make sure you treat her extra well
on birthdays and holidays.
Not having a family...
is a very lonely and painful thing.
So what was it you wanted to know?
You didn't write that
Cheon Seong Gil article.
I co-wrote it with a junior reporter.
If you don't want to talk about it,
forget it.
Well, anyway, thanks to that article,
Kingfisher's reputation was saved.
Is Kingfisher still giving you
the runaround?
They came back with a vengeance.
They've never operated on
such a tight schedule before.
If they take another break like this,
they'll be on track to wipe out
every criminal in the world.
This is the second one.
- What is?
- The hiatus.
There was one eight years ago.
Around the time of the World Cup,
after that incident.
Was it for nine months?
When they came back that time,
everyone was curious too.
Wondering what could have happened
during that time...
You know what happened to me
during that time, right?
I met Yu Bo Na.
Did you save Kwon Tae Sung that day?
Yes.
Why?
Because I wanted to.
It could have been dangerous.
It could have been, but luckily it wasn't.
You were secretly happy back then.
When Kingfisher returned
after the first hiatus.
I thought you'd be happy this time too.
You used to be so desperate
to meet Kingfisher.
What, have you lost interest now?
I can't meet them.
What happened after that?
He saved me.
And I came back.
Then...
That's right. It was my husband.
He's the one who made me come back.
They shouldn't have come back.
This time.
He also made me return as Kingfisher.
They should have stayed away.
It was Kwon Tae Sung. That's him.
(December 2018)
It's cold now, so when it gets warmer...
How about we talk about it then?
I made this decision
after thinking about it for a long time.
I know.
But you never know.
Maybe you'll change your mind...
when flowers bloom,
and the spring wind blows.
I don't want to do anything anymore.
Take a vacation, starting today.
Take as much time off as you need.
Yes, you should take a trip.
What do you say?
Does anyone have a travel recommendation
for Yu Bo Na?
Somewhere with nice mountains
and fresh air.
A place where
she doesn't have to do a thing.
Well, that would be...
How about here?
It's quiet, there's no one around,
and your phone won't work.
And I hear they serve three meals a day.
Right, for a trip, you need the ocean.
It really clears your head, you know?
Right, you can take
a boat ride too. It's perfect.
You should go there.
If you still feel the same when back,
I'll accept your resignation.
Okay?
(Unrim Mountain Lodge)
I wonder why she's acting like that.
She's not even eating.
She skipped another meal.
I'm really worried.
(A Bona Fide Killer)
Bo Na, what do you think of
when you see icicles?
That they'd be perfect for hitting
a vital point in one go.
I've never really found
anything to be pretty.
I'll show you
plenty of them from now on.
They say all the roads up the mountain
have been closed...
since yesterday afternoon.
I think we're stranded.
Bo Na.
Why did you do it right after
you got out of prison?
This is all because you cops
can't catch Kingfisher.
To me, Kingfisher is nothing
but a psychopathic murderer.
You're the family of one of the victims.
Can I borrow this for the weekend?
I have a confession to make.
I know who Kingfisher is.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)